

### **PROFILE**

9+ years as a software engineer

13+ year cancer survivor, Dad x2, cycling enthusiast, Colorado transplant,
& avid Cardinals fan

Adaptable, honest, & conscientious; hard worker, congenial, willing to lead, & high aptitude for problem solving

### CONTACT

2065 Magnolia Garden Dr O'Fallon, Missouri

314-324-4818

blakelmyers@gmail.com

#### **EDUCATION**

Washington University - St Louis Graduated Cum Laude Masters in Computer Science, 2016

University of Missouri - St Louis Graduated Magna Cum Laude Bachelor in Computer Science, 2011

# **BLAKE MYERS**

#### SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### SKILLS

- C++, C#, JavaScript, Python, HTML, XML, SQL, OpenGL, Java
- DevOps, Agile software development, SAFe
- Git, Jira, Jenkins, Artifactory
- Visual Studio, GLStudio, Blender, WordPress, Xcode

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### BOEING, SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

JUN 2018 - PRESENT

- Product Owner of Scrum team, responsible for backlog of tasks
- Developed and coordinated requirements with customers and stakeholders
- Managed a dozen team members working several different projects concurrently
- Developed display software for different mission systems platforms
- Responsible for reviewing code for quality and functionality
- Served as mentor to new engineers on tools and code development
- Came up to speed on new architecture and complex code quickly
- Received numerous Boeing Pride awards for outstanding work on assigned project

## BOEING, MID-LEVEL SOFTWARE ENGINEER JUN 2014 - JUN 2018

- Developed automation tools in C# for data processing
- Led small team in year long project involving new pilot UI for an aircraft platform
- Coordinated target builds and testing for embedded systems
- Supported software development on demos involving rapid prototyping for future aircraft capabilities

#### BOEING, ENTRY SOFTWARE ENGINEER MAY 2011 - JUN 2014

- Worked on build team, optimizing build scripts and tools
- Developed test and architecture documents, followed by development of code, and integration testing on hardware of real time embedded systems